Music
Sticky floors and dim lights, another Friday night
My old guitar case open wide
For tips that barely hide the cost of strings and gas to roam
This town I call my home
But every chord I strike feels right
Baiting this smoky light
They say this ain't a life that's just a phase
Lost in a million hazy days
But when I see those few who sing along
I know this is where I belong
Cause I'm playing for the ones who understand
This one out six string in my hand
From the sty ball stage I cast my plea
Dreaming of a stadium wild and free
But tonight it's just you and me
Yeah, tonight it's just you and me
Oh, the crowd is small but the spirit's bold
A story waiting to unfold
So I'll poster on the wall today
A band I used to play with
Back when we were kids so keen
Now they're on the silver screen
It stings a little
I won't lie as another lonely hour drips by
But the rhythm of the kick drum keeps me whole feeding
This hungry soul, they say this ain't a life that's just a phase
Lost in a million hazy days
But when I see those few who sing along
I know this is where I belong
Cause I'm playing for the ones who understand
This one out six string in my hand
From the sty ball stage I cast my plea
Dreaming of a stadium wild and free
But tonight it's just you and me
Yeah, tonight it's just you and me
Maybe tomorrow the stars will align
Maybe this dream will finally be mine
But there's a magic in this humble sound
On this hologramic ground
A song that's just a phase
But when I see those few who sing along
Cause I'm playing for the ones who understand
This one out six string in my hand
From the sty ball stage I cast my plea
Dreaming of a stadium wild and free
But tonight it's just you and me
Yeah, tonight it's just you and me